get up!
I don't know Shut it up!
Woah!
Ah!
It's my dream to explore the world!
Sailing far and wide!
Take me with you!
We should leave promptly!
You really think we'd go for that?
That's enough out of you.
I've been held back for far too long.
I want to escape this suffocating island.
Please, free me from these chains.
Lord Odin, no. Stop that.
Raise your head. I'm sorry.
Weren't you just trying
to kill our captain?
I beg you. Enough.
This man is a pirate, not an ally.
You're a scourge.
Leave this country before it's too late.
Well, I would leave if I could.
But as you can see, our ship
was damaged on the way here.
So that presents a slight problem.
That won't do at all.
I'll help you repair it!
Listen well, I cannot have you
tempting Lord Odin like this.
Repair the ship quickly and go!
That's exactly my intention.
Stop jogging your feet!
Bring it here!
Hey!
You ready for a snack break? Huh?
We've got some grub for you.
Dig in!
No need to be shy.
Oh!
That looks good!
The flavor of a far-off land!
And what freightel is this?
It's alcohol made from grapes.
So many things out there I need to see.
Show me more!
Take me with you.
I want to solve every mystery in the world
You're not the type to
serve under someone.
I can see it already I can't
just let anyone on my ship.
Do you know what happens when there
are too many selfish people around?
People like you, I mean.
It's too hot.
It's not pretty.
I learned that the hard way
with the last ship I was on.
Why not set sail on your own?
I've tried over and over again, but
every damn time it ends in failure.
I may be strong, but that doesn't
mean I can navigate a ship.
Then give up on sailing and
do whatever your job is.
This country is suffocating me, all right?
I need to be free!
Listen, Whitebeard.
The land of Wano has a law that
strictly bars people from leaving here.
Lord Odin is now the Daimyo of Kaido,
so it would be inexcusable
for him to break that law.
Don't tell him about that! Hmm.
Well, good to know.
Seems you and I are on the same page.
I don't want your Daimyo
on my ship, either.
Do you think I care about
some stuffy old laws?
How insightful of you.
Yes, Lord Odin is
indispensable to our land.
That's enough! You'll be fine!
Take me to Sea Whitebeard! Please!
Help me!
I don't want to be the type, yo!
No!
Please don't make me go home!
This place is suffocating, I tell you!
Untie me, you beasts!
How cruel!
I won't give up!
You cannot stop me!
White beard!
Wait for me!
You think there's only
five islands in the world?
Not even close!
What?
Try 10 million, maybe
even 20 million, or more.
Geez, you guys don't know anything.
Sailing the world is a blast.
You should try it.
The world out there is a big place.
There's so many islands, you
could never hope to see them all.
Sneaking off?
Where might you be going?
It's quite late.
You frighten me half to death.
Where are you going?
Does the daimyo need your
permission to take a piss?
Give me a break.
It's nothing.
Do take care, Lord Odin.
The night can be cold.
Ridiculous.
Odin won't be happy we snuck
away at night like this.
A pity, since he was so strong, he
might have been an asset to the crew.
It really seemed like pops liked
him too, I thought he'd say yes!
Ah, what are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with us!
Hypothetically, even if I
did take a liking to him,
we still couldn't bring him along with us.
That would be like kidnapping royalty.
Did you leave him that
treasure chest like I told you?
We owe them for all the food
and supplies they gave us.
What the hell is that?
You pirates thought you could
pull one over on me, huh?
Well, too bad!
Odin!
Don't let me on that ship!
Not so fast!
I know you think you're clever, my lord,
but you're not getting away that easily.
Now come with me!
That idiot!
Show me the world!
Keep you with you! Why, man?
We need you here!
You're to feed the next Shogun!
Sorry, pal, no means no, but
good luck ruling or whatever.
I'm letting you loose now.
Wait just a moment. Huh?
I'm concerned about the man
who's chasing after Odin.
Bring him up here.
What a pain!
Now, everyone hold on!
Don't worry about those morons from Wano!
We're about to fly over those balls!
No!
Lord Odin is gone!
Whitebeard's ship has left the port, too.
My greatest fears are coming true.
Ezo's gone, too.
Even the doggie and kitty.
Don't cry, Okiku.
Instead of fearing the worst, we
should search for them as a team.
You with me?
Start the search!
Cover the whole country!
Hey, he's had enough!
You can't let Lord Odin die!
Pull up the chain!
We need him!
The future of our country
rests on his shoulders!
Listen, kid.
You saw me tell him no again and again.
He's the one who turned his
back on that country of yours.
We're on my ship, and that means
we're gonna play by my rules.
Don't do this!
I'm begging you!
That man is dangerous.
I can't let him force his way on board.
I have to protect my family first.
If you want to stop him,
talk him down yourself.
Listen up, Odin.
Three days.
You hang onto that chain for three days.
Then I'll let you come aboard.
Do you swear it?
All your life?
Yeah.
You have my word!
I can't tell.
Is Odin still there?
Uh, yeah, he is.
But he's looking, uh, not great.
Between the waves and everything
else crashed into his face.
He's pretty busted up.
Only one hour left, Odin!
You got this! Let's go!
Hey, you shouldn't be
cheering for the guy.
But Pop said he could join
us if he pulls us off.
Don't you get it?
He's gonna become a member of our crew!
Huh?
Oh?
We'll be your new Gourmet?
Oh!
You can do it!
Just hang on!
Odin! Yeah! Attaboy!
Let's do it, Oda!
Kick him off now! Come on!
Yeah, come on, Oda!
Those fools.
I don't care if it's you, shit.
No one treats my lord like
this and gets away with it.
I'll make you free!
Keep it unloaded! Come on!
I'll do it, Oda!
Almost there, buddy!
Hang on!
Lord Odin, no!
No!
Take your hands off of me!
What a babe!
And she's so classy!
Why are you running?
We'll take you to Wano
just like you asked.
We've got a nice big ship waiting for you.
You don't have to be scared.
We won't hurt you.
I know you won't.
Your vessel is a slave ship, after all.
If you hurt me, I'll be worth less.
I should have fled the moment I
saw your wicked-looking faces.
How foolish of me.
You're gonna drown, girl.
There's nowhere left to run.
Just give up.
You're wrong.
I can still escape.
Put that big sword away.
I promise we'll treat you nice.
You'll be our little treasure, okay?
It's time.
I must escape into the future once again.
What the hell is that thing?
I see myself!
I heard a young woman's
voice crying out for help.
It can speak.
Are you all right, miss?
You are injured, are you?
Oh, my!
It may hurt you.
What?
No, I'm just a little shaken up.
But wait, does that mean
you came here to save me?
I did.
I'm so glad you're all right.
You're in much worse shape than me.
Come on, stay with me, please.
Odin disappeared.
What happened? Where did he go? Damn it.
There were only a few minutes left to go.
He was so close to making it, but
he couldn't hold on. He's dead!
I don't think it's fair
what you did to him, Pops!
Yeah, he gave it his best back there!
You should have let him join us!
Lord Odin!
Hey, stop me!
Let go of me now!
Answer me!
Lord Odin!
He's recovering so fast.
I didn't realize he was a human.
Yes!
Wow! Wow!
A fierce struggle, but I still
couldn't get on Whitebeard's ship.
All those dreams of touring around the
world just sailed right away, but no matter!
I still did it!
I set foot on foreign soil for
the first time ever! Finally!
So cheery.
My adventure has begun at last!
The land of Wano is far behind me now!
The world is my oyster! I'm free!
Don't jump around so much!
You're healing fast, but you're
not fully recovered yet! Huh?
I see!
So you're the woman who
nursed me back to health!
Yes, sort of.
Thank you very much!
Oh no, it's the least I
could do after you saved me!
Truly, I am in your debt, sir.
Well, miss, we're both safe now,
and that's all that matters.
By the way, did I hear you say
that you're from the land of Wano?
That I am, yes.
And speaking of which,
I've come all the way to a foreign land,
but you're dressed like you're
from the flower capital.
I would have thought you'd
wear something more exotic.
Well, the truth is, since I was a child,
it's been my dream to
visit the land of Wano.
When you return home, would you be
so kind as to take me along with you?
He's annoyed.
That's her!
Right over there!
We're counting on you, Captain Karma!
Six hearts! Wow, fascinating!
Back at home, we don't have
anybody built like that!
Huh?
Hey!
I thought you guys said there
was a monster protecting her!
Huh? That's funny! Where'd it go?
I mean, it's way too big to hide!
Well, you're back!
Can't get enough.
Then who are you?
Don't act like you know us, bastard!
Huh?
Did all of you hit your
heads or something?
Should have known a high-class lady
would have had a bodyguard with her.
But it'll be worth the price she fetches.
I'll kick your ass and then sell you both!
Let's run away.
There are too many of them.
My first fight overseas.
I can't wait.
It's the White Beard Pirates—this man,
Karma eventually became an
associate of the White Beard Pirates
and even fought beside them
during the war in Marineford.
Come aboard!
Let's go.
Huh, but I let go of the chain back there.
What made you change your mind?
One woman screams and you throw
your dream away—quite the softy.
Aren't you?
Hurry before I change my mind!
We're setting out on an amazing adventure,
one beyond your wildest dreams.
Ready, little?
ready little
brother.
Are you sure, Waikichi? Hm?
Are you talking to me?
Let's set sail!
Odin!
We're so glad you're alive!
I was starting to think
we lost you to the sea.
Yeah, what a relief.
Glad to be here. Thank you.
Bob's gave you a rough
time back there, huh?
Real nasty stuff.
What a jerk, huh?
Hey, I heard that.
You're alive.
It's such a relief to see you safe, sir.
Yes, and better than ever, my friend.
We're here, too.
Dog Storm!
Cat Piper!
Where the hell did you come from?
We figured Yugarra would get
on the ship one way or another,
so we snuck on and hid
before it left Wano.
Wherever Yugarra go, we'll follow.
Stewards!
A while back, you said you were
going to make me pay, didn't you?
If you want to throw me
into the sea, then do it.
Maybe I will someday.
Miss, what's your name?
Oh, pleasure to meet you.
I'm Toki.
Thank you so much for helping me.
So, um, if it's not a bother, could
you take me to the land of Wano?
She's annoyed.
I'll help out however I can.
So please let me stay on board this ship.
Do as you like!
Every sight, every sound,
and every experience that I have will
be faithfully chronicled in my journal.
Enemy ship!
Prepare for battle, everyone!
Here we go!
No! Not yet! Please!
Why not?
There! You see?
I sank it! Idiot!
That wasn't the plan!
You don't get how pirates
work at all, do you?
Oh, plunder!
You gotta plunder the ship first!
So many things I've
never experienced before.
What is this place?
Tall buildings of curious make.
Bubble encased trees
undulating like jelly.
Odin, wait!
We don't know if it's safe!
A world of wonders.
No way!
Odin!
A chill like none other.
A heat like none other.
Odin!
Hang on, I got you!
Adventure, here I come!
Peculiar plants.
Come here.
Astonishing animals.
Humongous humans!
Step back, kid!
All right!
Wa-ha-ha!
Strength like I'd never seen!
And courage!
But more than that, ideas.
Every day my eyes are opened in new ways.
I realize how narrow my vision was
before I embarked on this journey.
I see now that I am only a tiny
piece of a great wide world!
How old am I?
I'm 26, but I was born long ago,
so technically I'm 800 years old.
So what you're saying is: you're
young but you're old as dirt.
It seems that even leaping through time
is possible; the world is a big place.
I have learned that this world consists of
four large seas and one
long narrow waterway.
And apparently the planet
itself is round like a dumpling.
What a mysterious thing.
What do you think?
Enjoying the voyage?
Certainly.
The world is amazing.
I want to see more.
I'm glad to hear you're having fun.
What is that?
A map.
In these vast seas, the land
of Wano is hardly a speck.
So, which region is
your family from, Toki?
I'm not sure.
All I know is that both of my
parents were from the land of Wano.
Even if that doesn't seem like much,
Wano is the only place I have left to go.
But I'm afraid the ship won't
make it there for quite some time.
I am sorry.
It's fine.
I'm rather enjoying my travels with you.
Because when you and I are together, I
feel like I'm exactly where I need to be.
Why is that?
I wonder.
How peculiar. A mystery.
Hey, guys.
Where'd Lord Oden run off to?
Oh, there.
Don't bother them.
I soon learned that
Whitebeard has an enemy.
The Navy's here. Let's retreat.
Why did we flee?
They look like a worthy challenge.
We should have fought them.
You don't know the Navy, huh?
It's a big organization.
Even if we take them down today, more
and more ships will come after us. Hm?
Wow, so there's a group that
controls the entire world, huh?
A mighty adversary, indeed!
Yeah, wait till you've traveled some more.
Then you can decide how mighty they are.
Your country's still free, after all.
Oh?
Ah, nothing in the paper today, either.
What?!
Another story on Whitebeard?!
But we're causing trouble too!
Hey, I'm still reading, dummy.
Anyway, Whitebeard has that
Wano samurai on his crew.
Seems like that guy's doing
crazy stuff all the time.
Hey, Captain.
A samurai from a land
shield away from the world.
Sure hope I get to meet him someday.
Thank you.